hooyou.com 2017-05-28

# Zhang & Associates, P.C. - Immigration Attorneys in New York, Houston, Silicon Valley, Seattle, Chicago, Austin, Los Angeles

## **Purpose and Scope**

Thisprivacy policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit hooyou.com or buy products or services from us. 

**Information We Gather**

Hooyou.com collects user information in the following two ways: 1) data we collect when users contact us by email, contacting form, or online support links; 2) data that users voluntarily provide by signing up for our membership services and by inquiring about our product and service information. 

**Personal Information**

We use the personal information you provide voluntarily to send information you've requested and to fulfill orders. The specific use of your personal information varies, depending on how you contact us: 

  * When you sign up to membership services or inquiry product and service information, you provide email address. We never sell or release your email address you provide to third party. 
  * When you contact us, we may ask for your name, address, phone number and email address so we can reply to you. 

We release personal information when we believe that its release is appropriate in order to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Hooyou.com Information Technology, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

**Tracking Information**

We analyze our site usage by tracking information such as traffic flow, pageviews, search terms, and click-throughs. We use this information to improve our site only and do not share any information with advertisers that can identify an individual user. 

**Services**

This site contains links to other sites. Hooyou.com Information Technology is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites. 

**Notification of Changes**

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website. If we decide to use personal information in a way different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify those affected users via email. 

**Contact the Website**

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, feel free to [contact us](http://www.hooyou.com/contact_zbg/index.html).
